Nofrialdi

Full Stack Engineer



aldi.fasive@gmail.com



0896-1202-2458





Github

Bachelor of Information Systems with interest in programming. Have an understanding of application and web development, as well as database management. Skilled in creating websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript and able to create websites using the ReactJs and Nextjs frameworks besides also understanding the Java and PHP programming languages. I have experience as an assistant programming instructor and have also been an Android developer. With the experience and understanding I have, I hope to become a full stack engineer in the future.

Experience

Revou

Software engineering associate

Aug, 2023 - Dec, 2023

- Create a Teladoc website UI/UX design using Figma and implement it on the website using the NextJS framework
- help create a growink website ui/ux using figma and implement it in the form of a website using the nextjs framework
- Serves as a team leader who leads the team in the development stages of the Teledoc website and Growink website and ensures that all tasks are completed on time according to the deadline.

CV. Bina Kreasi Informatika

Jan, 2018 - Nov, 2019

Programming assistant instructor

- Assist training at TNI Headquarters in the field of programming, especially website and Android training, through a structured curriculum.
- installed 40 computers that did not have the required applications before the training began, such as XAMPP, Android Studio, and Visual Studio Code.
- Training 40 TNI Headquarters students how to create websites from basic HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to using the CodeIgniter framework
- I trained 40 students at TNI Headquarters on how to make Android applications using the Android Studio application using Java and XML.

PT. Fedora

Sep, 2016 - Dec, 2017

Android developer

- Create UI/UX designs for Android applications for clients using the Figma application.
- Implement the UI/UX design into the application using Android Studio using the Java and XML programming languages.
- Connect the application with the database that has been provided by the team.
- Carry out maintenance on the applications created, starting with bug fixes and application optimization.

STMIK Jayakarta

Aug, 2015 - Jul, 2016

Assistant lecturer

- Help the lecturer teach in the classroom and deliver material to the students.
- Help fill in lecture activities and replace the lecturer leading the class if the lecturer is unable to attend.
- Create questions and answers for students; help compile course syllabi.

Education

Revou

Jan 2023 - Jul 2023

Full Stack Software Engineering

• At Revou, I learned how to create a website, from the basics of HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Typescript to creating a website using the React JS and Next JS frameworks.

Apart from that, I also learned how to create a UI/UX and a backend using Nest JS.

STMIK Jayakarta

Sep 2013 - April 2017

Bachelor of Computer Science

• I graduated from STMIK Jayakarta with the title "Human Respiratory System Application Design for Android-Based Primary Schools". I graduated with a GPA of 3.5.

Skills

Technical Skill

- Frontend: HTML, CSS, Xml, Javascript, Bootstrap, Tailwiness
- Framework : React.js, Next.js, Codeigniter
- Database : MySql, Postgresql
- Backend: Php, Nestjs, Java
- Service architecktures: RestAPI
- DevOps: Docker, Gcp (Google Cloud Platform)

Soft Skill

- Collaboration and Teamwork
- Time Management
- Problem-Solving Skills
- Communication

Project

• Web Portofolio

- <u>Github Repository</u>
- <u>Demo</u>
- Techstack: Html, Css, React.js, Javascrpict, Tailwiness

• Web Markilang

- <u>Github Repository</u>
- <u>Demo</u>
- Techstack: Html, Css, Next.js, Typescript, Tailwincss

Web Teledoc

- Github Repository
- Demo
- Techstack: Html, Css, React JS, Typescript, Tailwiness

• Web Growink

- Github Repository
- <u>Demo</u>
- Techstack: Html, Css, React JS, Java Script, Tailwiness

Web Wareg

- Github Repository
- <u>Demo</u>
- Techstack: Html, Css, Typescript, Nextjs, Tailwiness

• Web Revou FSSE student management

- <u>Github Repository</u>
- <u>Demo</u>
- Techstack: Html, Css, Typescript, Nextjs, Tailwincss

• Web Revou FSSE community

- <u>Github Repository</u>
- <u>Demo</u>
- Techstack: Html, Css, Javascript